MUNSEONG JEONG

Mobile: 0452462858

Email: jmunseng@gmail.com

Carlton, VIC 3053

Portfolio: https://www.leonjeong.com/

A fast learner and a passionate programmer with around 1 years of frontend experience. I am experienced in front-end development using numerous programming languages/tools including HTML, CSS, JS, React, NodeJS, Java, MySQL and Git. During the university I also used PHP, C++, C#, Python languages on assignment projects. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. My communication and teamwork skills have improved a lot from previous working experience. I also adapt quickly to different working environments and I am a good team player that received many positive feedback from colleagues.

EXPERIENCE

FrontEnd Developer

May 2022- Present

Trans Tasman Energy Group

Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

TTEG is providing solutions of energy requirements for the large, small and medium businesses.

Which using self developed customer management system.

responsibilities were:

- Created Retailer, Company, Council and Association list and detail pages.
- Fetch the data from API then filter or sort them.
- Technologies used: React, Typescript, Material UI, Git, Bitbucket,
- Agile mode develop environment
- Deploy the website to the server.
- Use design tool to create the layout of the website.
- Communicated with customers to discuss their needs.

Rider Operations Oct 2019 - Present

EASI Australia pty Itd

Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

EASI Australia is running the most popular Asian food delivery platform in Australia. My responsibilities were:

- managed about 200 riders in Australia to help the platform to improve order capacity;
- helped riders to solve different issues they have during work;
- solved the conflicts and communication problems among merchants, riders and customers;
- improved communication and teamwork skills.

Online Store Manager

May 2015 - Sep 2017

DamingGlass

Pocheon, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea. My responsibilities were:

- developed online shopping platform from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- managed product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as Naver shopping, Gmarket and 11 street store, including creating images via Photoshop;
- translated documents between Chinese and Korean.

Web Designer

Jul 2013 - Apr 2014

샵피라 (Sappira)

Uijeongbu, Gyeonggi-do, Korea

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea. My responsibilities were:

- created and maintained promotion web pages, mainly used PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript;
- maintained product content across different online shopping platforms, including editing product information and creating photos via Photoshop;

Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2012 - Apr 2013

Seoul, Korea

KISKorea

Kiskorea provides an online international tourism platform and a mobile gaming platform. My responsibilities were:

- coded and maintained static web pages from the design, including both tourism and mobile gaming platforms' user interface pages and admin management pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and W2UI;
- implemented functionalities that get data from database, mainly based on Java and MySQL;
- tested, debugged and fixed errors in web applications.

SKILLS

Programming Languages/Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, C, C#,

Python, numpy, Java,

Databases: MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB

Source Control: Git, GitHub **IDE**: Visual Studio Code, EditPlus

Communication Skills: communicate effectively in English, Mandarin and Korean.

EDUCATION

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics

Kaplan BUSINESS SCHOOL Dockland

Majors: Business Analytics

Bachelor of Information Technology

Deakin University, Burwood

Majors: Application Development

Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

Mar 2018 - Nov 2020